Did you actually physically
ring the bell yesterday?
I'm super honored to have rung the
bell, to be honest I didn't know it
until 30 seconds before.  An
incredible thought.  I am truly very grateful.
What do you do at Benny Spoons?
Finance.  I do what it takes, I'm
telling you the truth.  Then I imagine you
worked hard for this IPO,
a lot.  It all started with a
more accounting job.  We
converted the financial statements with the
accounting principles needed to be listed
here.  Months of work also on accounting and
then the construction of the
prospectus began.  That was perhaps the most
difficult part to manage because it combined
consultants, legal people, financial people,
perhaps the most difficult part was
managing such a complicated process
with so many people.
And you often work with Luca, you were saying?  Yes,
with this enormous fortune.  I started
working with Checco, to be honest,
almost immediately.  At the beginning I was taking care of the
business plan for Bending Spoons and there
weren't that many spooners
doing it and the banks had started
asking us for a real business, no, with
cash flow, which we didn't
really do before, it was a bit full up to the point of being able to raise
money.  It wasn't as good right away
as the business is now, but
we got there and I've been lucky enough to
work with Checco ever since.
Amazing experience.  Yeah.